<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>1001 Pots 2025</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/1001-pots/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/1001-pots/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we went to 1001 pots in Val David. It&amp;rsquo;s the biggest pottery expo in Quebec and it happens every year. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t super into it in the beginning but I&amp;rsquo;m glad I went. We went with Lukus and his studio, with Mel and Aaron and her friend in my car.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some highlights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love this form&amp;hellip; I am gonna try to make some stuff like this . I&amp;rsquo;ll probably need a special rib. Update : I have acquired a special rib
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/1001-pots/PXL_20250712_182639772.jpg&#34;
	width=&#34;3072&#34;
	height=&#34;4080&#34;
	srcset=&#34;http://localhost:1313/posts/1001-pots/PXL_20250712_182639772_hu64f690fbf3c45ba5fdf64ab023ce6571_2668220_480x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 480w, http://localhost:1313/posts/1001-pots/PXL_20250712_182639772_hu64f690fbf3c45ba5fdf64ab023ce6571_2668220_1024x0_resize_q75_box.jpg 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;75&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;180px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This painting is done with something called &amp;ldquo;china paint&amp;rdquo; that gets luster-fired on. It would make it not dishwasher safe but it should allow me to explore drawing on my pieces in the cleanest way possible ![[PXL_20250712_190651080.jpg]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My favourite two potters at the thing:
![[PXL_20250712_191412172.jpg]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![[PXL_20250712_195029880.jpg]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I almost bought dishes from each potter and that red jewellry box from the first potter, but then decided against it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This glaze application is amazing. I gotta start experimenting with layered glazes, they produce such cool results.
![[Pasted image 20250719073920.jpg]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bought 2 teacup looking things from this potter because their glaze was my favourite and I wanted cups for drinking green tea.
![[Pasted image 20250719074124.jpg]]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then we went for ice cream and went home. I had my AC fixed specifically for this trip and it was worth it haha, we would have died otherwise. I might have been over 30 C outside, and it was humid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By going with Lukus I could also ask him a ton of questions, so that was super cool. He told me that he made a bowl with tenmoku glaze and got crystals out of it by just firing it twice, which means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to do a speical firing. He also tuaght me about china paint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luca&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
